NIKOLA KUBUROVIĆ

Frontend Developer

Kosjerić, Serbia

Mobile phone: +381 63 88 64 664

E-mail: kubnik@gmail.com

GitHub: github.com/NikolaKuburovic
Behance: behance.net/nikolakuburovic
Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/nikola-kuburovic

PROFILE

I'm a frontend developer with extensive experience in graphic design.

Creativity and analytics are equally important parts of everything I have done in my career.

I also have extensive experience in communication and cooperation with people. It is a pleasure to share ideas and look for solutions with the creative-minded. I enjoy learning and gathering new knowledge and with the same enjoyment, I share the knowledge I have.

EXPERIENCE

2018 – Present

FRONTEND DEVELOPER | GRAPHIC DESIGNER | MARKETING MANAGER

Aqua Lines | Kosjeric, Serbia Swimming pool company

Key Responsibilities and Achievements

- Design and maintenance of the company's website (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP)
- Design and maintenance of a website for after-sales customer care (WordPress, PHP)
- Professional editing and retouching of photos of all the company's projects for the website and marketing materials
- Analyzed, tested, and implemented the best product database software solution that helps track production as well as sales in the most efficient way
- Created a new visual identity of the company by rebranding
- Developed and implemented digital marketing campaigns that attracted thousands of website visitors
- Designed all marketing materials (catalogs, brochures, flyers, business cards)
- Research and analysis of potential business development
- Establishing and maintaining business partnerships with international companies

2019 – Present

PRIVATE TUTOR

Teaching students Programming, Algorithms, Data Structures

2003 – Present FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Worked for clients from the USA, Israel, UK, Sweden, Canada, and Serbia.

Designed Logos, Stationeries, Catalogs, Brochures, T-Shirts

2003 – 2016 BUSINESS OWNER | ENTREPRENEUR

Vijemont | Kosjerić, Serbia

Production and wholesale of hygiene paper products

EDUCATION

2011 – 2021 ENGINEER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES – Bachelor's Studies

Faculty of Information Technology, Metropolitan University Belgrade, Serbia

1999 – 2003 BASKETBALL, STRENGTH AND FITNESS COACH

Sports Academy, Belgrade, Serbia

TECHNICAL COURSES COMPLETED

Angular - The Complete Guide (2022 Edition) – Udemy Front-End Development - Treehouse

Full-Stack React, Python, and GraphQL – Udemy

SKILLS | INTERESTS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, ReactJS, GraphQL, MySQL, PHP, WordPress, Java, C#, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

SOFTWARE PROJECTS

Music Box Music Sharing WebApp - (ReactJS, Graphql, Django)

Recipes WebApp - (Angular) – *ongoing* Web Library WebApp - (Angular, PHP, MySQL)

Weather Mobile App - (Android)

University Courses WebApp - (Java, Spring, MySQL)

English-Serbian Dictionary PC Program - (Java)
Library Manager PC Program - (C#)

Product Catalog PC Program – (Python, SQLite3)

Space Driver PC Game - (Java)

LANGUAGES

English Full professional proficiencyRussian Limited working proficiency

Serbian Native speaker

German Beginner

OTHER SOFTWARE SKILLS

CorelDraw, QuarkXPress, Adobe InDesign, Spring framework, Unix/Linux, Microsoft Project, SAP PowerDesigner, Google Ads, Google Analytics

RELEVANT UNIVERSITY COURSEWORK

Introduction to Object-Oriented Programming Introduction to Software Engineering

Management of Software Development Projects

Web Systems 1

Web Systems 2

Scripting Languages

Human-Computer Interaction

Databases

Development of Mobile Applications

Safety and Data Security

Mathematics in IT

Discrete Structures

C/C++ Programming Language

Professional Communication

Programming in C#

Distributed Systems

OTHER

Musician and songwriter. Sang and played bass guitar in two bands (released three albums). Love reading books.

Half-marathon runner.